couponclue.com 2016-08-30

# Save Money with Latest Coupon Codes and Deals :: Coupon Clue Promo Codes 2015

####  What information do we collect ? 

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your : e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

####  What do we use your information for ? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways. To personalize your experience ( your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs ) To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries or other requests or questions.  
Note : If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

####  How do we protect your information ? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

####  Do we use cookies ? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

####  Do we disclose any information to outside parties ? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

####  Third party links. 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

####  Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance. 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

####  Use of Site Browsing History. 

By using website couponclue.com, you consent to collection, storage, and use of your browsing history on this website. We share this information with trusted 3rd parties that use it to show you marketing communications of interest only. While no Personally Identifiable Information is shared, we respect your right to privacy hence this transparent disclosure. In addition, we respect your right to opt out. If you want to opt out from this program, please click on the link below and select the appropriate option on the destination page – Opt Out Page.  
In addition, most setup your browser software to reject 3rd party cookies. In addition, you can opt out of several similar programs by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site.

#### Your Consent.

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.   
http://www.couponclue.com
